newswatch33.com 2016-12-06

# Privacy Policy

Effective April, 2011

At InformationAboutDiabetes.com we understand the importance of protecting your privacy. Our Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personal information collected when anyone is on our site or uses the services we provide; it neither addresses nor applies to individuals or third party practices over which we have no control. This includes but is not limited to cookies which may be used by our advertisers.

### At InformationAboutDiabetes.com, information is collected in three ways:

  1. Via the information that you provide to us when you enter your registration information, which requires an email address as well as some basic information about you. You do not need to register to use our site, and if you do register you may omit certain information; however, please be aware that doing so may restrict you from enjoying the full range of our web site. If you choose to create a profile with a Sign-In Name, Bio, Recent Posts etc., InformationAboutDiabetes.com makes it possible for other users to browse the site for this information.
  2. Via the information that your computer automatically provides to us. Via our server, InformationAboutDiabetes.com collects your IP address, cookie information, and the pages you visit in an effort to help us administer and improve our site. Our servers use cookies to enable us to recognize your computer and facilitate use of our site. They do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information gathered by cookies with any personal information provided by you through registration. You may disable cookies from the "help" toolbar on your internet browser.
  3. Via the information that you submit through forms on this site in conjunction with offers, surveys and other forms of solicitation.

### Third party companies

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

### Sharing Your Information

The information that is collected by InformationAboutDiabetes as detailed above may be shared with our partners and other third parties per opt-in agreement or other user consent obtained during the process of submitting personal information for a specific offer, survey, or other information-collecting campaign.

### Privacy Policy only effective for this site

This Policy pertains only to information collected directly through InformationAboutDiabetes.com. This Policy does not apply to personal information collected from offline resources and communications (e.g., postal letter or phone call). This Policy also does not apply to third party online resources to which the Deep Dive Media network of websites may link, where Deep Dive Media does not control the content, nor the privacy practices.

### Changes & Conditions of Use

Changes or amendments to our Privacy Policy may occur now and again as warranted. However, information is always and only subject to the policy in place at the time it is collected. Should we feel the need to execute a change in the Policy, we will announce the change on our website so that our users are made aware of the change and may act accordingly.

Finally, the conditions of use (visits to our website, including the information collected, our use of that information, and any future disputes regarding issues of privacy) are subject to both this Policy in addition to our Terms of Use.
